

roblav96@gmail.com



401-203-3195



New York, NY



Altruistic, ego-free, humble, open-minded



Leader, openly criticize, will take charge



Eager to learn, more eager

"If you want to go far, go



Public seminar speaker & event attendee



+2,000 GitHub contributions yearly



TypeScript

together"



Node.js



React.js

Vue.js



Tailwind



Amazon Web Services



Supabase



Vercel



Docker

Redis



PostgreSQL



MongoDB



Google Analytics



Electron



Sublime Text

## **Robert Laverty**

Full-Stack Software Engineer





#### **README.md**

I'm a Problem Solver. That statement can easily be validated by the numerous projects I've created from the ground up. Every project was developed because of a problem I had experienced myself. I've taken them from an idea, all the way to a minimum viable product and talking to investors. Throughout these endeavors I've learned how to efficiently identify a problem, produce a solution based on meaningful metrics, analytics, and A/B tests, market and sell the product, then scale to a larger audience. I want to put my extraordinary skill-sets to good use at your company and work with a team of your best innovators. Please don't hesitate to contact me if you have any questions. Thank you!

### **Experience**



#### RealCount - Lead Software Engineer

Jan 2024 - Current



Live music ticket sales data aggregator from all ticket platforms, used by artists, agencies, promoters, and venue owners





Jan 2023 - Nov 2023

















**ExaCare** - Founding Frontend Software Engineer Built the entire frontend from the ground up, precisely following a Figma design

May 2022 - Dec 2022

Sep 2018 - Feb 2022

Feb 2020 - Apr 2020

May 2019 - Oct 2019















Futon Media - Creator Instantly stream Movies and TV Shows via Emby Media



































































Robinhood Tools - Creator



TS (S) 🔻 💺 ‰ 🔌 😂 🔃



Kava Labs - Senior Full-Stack Software Engineer



Advanced tools and resources for trading equities on Robinhood









GetHuman - Senior Full-Stack Software Engineer

Sep 2016 - Aug 2017



Designed, developed, and deployed native mobile platform on iOS & Android using NativeScript



EMC Corporation - Full-Stack Software Engineer

Sep 2015 - Dec 2015 Helped develop scanner reporting front-end in an agile environment using scrum methodologies









# **Education**



Google Primer - Grow With Google Program

Insights from trusted industry experts insights from trusted industry experts into jargon-free interactive lessons featuring practical next steps for reaching your business or career goals



<u>University of Rhode Island</u> - Computer Science

Voluntarily resigned due to outdated curriculum

Sep 2009 - June 2010